genebase.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Genebase

## Personal Information

The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include the patient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. Agents and contractors of Genebase who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice, e.g. not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Genebase. Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices.

Genebase recognizes the important of privacy and enforces strict privacy controls for all DNA testing accounts.

Your personal information will only be used for the purpose of carrying out the services performed for you by Genebase and will not be used for any other purposes. By providing us with your personal information, you are agreeing that we may use the information for these purposes only. You can withdrawn your consent at any time, but if you do so, you will not be able to continue using the services provided on your account.

## Collection of Personal Information

Strict procedures have been put into place to safeguard personal information to prevent unauthorized access to personal information, both online and physically on site. If you have any specific questions or concerns about safety and security of personal information, you may contact us at support@genebase.com.

We only collect and use your personal information for the purpose of performing the services that you have requested and to manage your account and provide customer support. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need to correspond with you or process an order, it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. When you register from the Online Order Form, we use your information to process your order. We will also send you emails to confirm your order, and we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order. We do not disclose your personal information to anyone; except if in accordance with a legal obligation under a warrant. We do not share, rent or sell any information we collect online to any unaffiliated third party. We safeguard the integrity of our customers’ information. If you do not wish to set up your account online, you can also choose to call us directly to set up your account over the phone.

## Your Online Account

You are responsible for protecting your Account ID and password and any actions you take with them. You must not share your Account ID and password with anyone. If you suspect that your password has been compromised, for any reason, you should change it immediately. You can change your email address or your password at any time directly from your online account.

Your online access to your Genebase account is from a secure connection. Only authorized employees who are bound by a confidentiality agreement can help you to access your personal information in order to perform required duties such as providing you with technical support for your account. We may make updates to the Privacy Policy from time to time and recommend that you routinely check this page for changes.

If you have any questions or concerns pertaining to privacy matters related to your account please contact us at support@genebase.com.
